{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite food?",
      "options": ["Pizza", "Burger", "Shawarma", "Pasta"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is Adeeb from?",
      "options": ["Damascus", "Aleppo", "Homs", "Hama"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite hobby?",
      "options": ["Reading", "Gaming", "Coding", "Traveling"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite color?",
      "options": ["Blue", "Green", "Red", "Black"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite movie?",
      "options": ["Inception", "The Matrix", "Interstellar", "Avatar"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Adeeb's favorite football player?",
      "options": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Lionel Messi", "Mario Balotelli", "Neymar"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite season?",
      "options": ["Spring", "Summer", "Autumn", "Winter"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite type of music?",
      "options": ["Rock", "Pop", "Classical", "Phonk"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite sport to watch?",
      "options": ["Football", "Basketball", "Tennis", "Formula 1"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite dessert?",
      "options": ["Ice Cream", "Chocolate Cake", "CheeseCake", "Tiramisu"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's preferred method of transportation?",
      "options": ["Car", "Bicycle", "Public Transit", "Walking"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite pet?",
      "options": ["Dog", "Cat", "Monkey","Bird" ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "How does Adeeb view failure?",
      "options": ["As a challenge","As a loss", "As a learning opportunity", "As a setback"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Adeeb's favorite game on PS4?",
      "options": ["God of War", "Spider-Man", "The Last of Us 2", "Horizon Zero Dawn"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
     "question": "Which PS4 game series does Adeeb enjoy playing the most after The Last of Us?",
     "options": ["Uncharted", "God of War", "Detroit", "Red Dead Redemption"],
     "correctOption": 2,
     "points": 10
    }
  ]
}
